Git is not configured to allow long paths. This can cause issues with Shorebird's Flutter checkout. Please run 'git config --system core.longpaths true' to enable long paths.
Could not find an option named "--force".
To proxy an option to the flutter command, use the '--' --<option> syntax.

Example:

shorebird release android '--' --no-pub lib/main.dart

Usage: shorebird patch [arguments]
-h, --help                     Print this usage information.
    --dart-define              Additional key-value pairs that will be available as constants from the String.fromEnvironment, bool.fromEnvironment, and int.fromEnvironment constructors.
                               Multiple defines can be passed by repeating "--dart-define" multiple times.
    --dart-define-from-file    The path of a .json or .env file containing key-value pairs that will be available as environment variables.
                               These can be accessed using the String.fromEnvironment, bool.fromEnvironment, and int.fromEnvironment constructors.
                               Multiple defines can be passed by repeating "--dart-define-from-file" multiple times.
                               Entries from "--dart-define" with identical keys take precedence over entries from these files.
-p, --platforms                The platform(s) to to build this release for.
                               [aar, android, ios, linux, macos, ios-framework, windows]
    --build-name               A "x.y.z" string used as the version number shown to users.
                               For each new version of your app, you will provide a version number to differentiate it
                               from previous versions.
                               On Android it is used as "versionName".
                               On Xcode builds it is used as "CFBundleShortVersionString".
                               On Windows it is used as the major, minor, and patch parts of the product and file
                               versions.
    --build-number             An identifier used as an internal version number.
                               Each build must have a unique identifier to differentiate it from previous builds.
                               It is used to determine whether one build is more recent than another, with higher numbers indicating more recent build.
                               On Android it is used as "versionCode".
                               On Xcode builds it is used as "CFBundleVersion".
                               (defaults to "1.0")
-t, --target                   The main entrypoint file of the application.
    --flavor                   The product flavor to use when building the app.
    --release-version          The version of the associated release (e.g. "1.0.0").
                               If you are building an xcframework or aar, this number needs to match the host app's release version.
                               To target the latest release (e.g. the release that was most recently updated) use --release-version=latest.
    --allow-native-diffs       Patch even if native code diffs are detected.
                               NOTE: this is not recommended. Native code changes cannot be included in a patch and attempting to do so can cause your app to crash or behave unexpectedly.
    --allow-asset-diffs        Patch even if asset diffs are detected.
                               NOTE: this is not recommended. Asset changes cannot be included in a patch can cause your app to behave unexpectedly.
    --track                    The track to publish the patch to.
                               (defaults to "stable")
    --export-options-plist     Export an IPA with these options. See "xcodebuild -h" for available exportOptionsPlist keys (iOS only).
    --export-method            Specify how the IPA will be distributed (iOS only).

          [app-store]          Upload to the App Store
          [ad-hoc]             Test on designated devices that do not need to be registered with the Apple developer account.
                                   Requires a distribution certificate.
          [development]        Test only on development devices registered with the Apple developer account.
          [enterprise]         Distribute an app registered with the Apple Developer Enterprise Program.

    --[no-]codesign            Codesign the application bundle (iOS only).
                               (defaults to on)
-n, --dry-run                  Validate but do not upload the patch.
    --private-key-path         The path for a private key .pem file that will be used to sign the patch artifact.
    --public-key-path          The path for a public key .pem file that will be used to validate patch signatures.
    --public-key-cmd           Command that outputs a PEM-encoded public key to stdout for patch signature validation.
    --sign-cmd                 Command that reads data from stdin and outputs a base64 signature to stdout.
    --split-debug-info         In a release build, this flag reduces application size by storing Dart program symbols in a separate file on the host rather than
                               in the application. The value of the flag should be a directory where program symbol files can be stored for later use. These
                               symbol files contain the information needed to symbolize Dart stack traces. For an app built with this flag, the "flutter
                               symbolize" command with the right program symbol file is required to obtain a human readable stack trace.
    --min-link-percentage      The minimum link percentage (0-100) required in order to generate a patch (Apple platforms only).
                               
                               Patches with a lower link percentage than what is provided here will fail.
                               [0 (default), 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 27, 28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 40, 41, 42, 43, 44, 45, 46, 47, 48, 49, 50, 51, 52, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59, 60, 61, 62, 63, 64, 65, 66, 67, 68, 69, 70, 71, 72, 73, 74, 75, 76, 77, 78, 79, 80, 81, 82, 83, 84, 85, 86, 87, 88, 89, 90, 91, 92, 93, 94, 95, 96, 97, 98, 99, 100]

Run "shorebird help" to see global options.
